Your urgent reply for the product. Don’t miss out!
==========
Dear customer,
Good day,
how are you?

we are the amazon seller from A-yixian,
have you got the parcel we shipped to you?

we are writing to ask you if you have any problems about this item,
if it is, please contact us here,
we promise we can solve it well for you, do not worry,

if you are happy with the item you received, we sincerely wish you would still show your support in our amazon store,
and welcome back to purchase anything you need again.
 
Thanks a lot.
Best wishes