The information about your order
==========
Dear customer，
How are you.

This is Aiterwu shop seller from the Amazon.

You bought the item in our shop before, do you remember it?
May I know have you got the item now?

If you are satisfied with our product, can you please leave your good comment in the product page?
You know, your comment can help other customers get the useful information of the product.
Is this fine?

If you have any product problems, please feel free to contact me, i will try my best to help you.
Have a nice day!
Best wishes