Your order information
==========
Dear customer,
Good day!

We are AMA shop seller from Amazon shop.

You bought the product in our shop before, do you remember it?
we have sent you the product out very early.

may i know have you received the product now?

If you are satisfied with our product, we hope you can share your good experience under the product page. It can help other customer get some useful information before they buy it

if you have any problems, you can send me the email to us,
we will offer you the professional solutions in time.

Wish you have a nice day!
Best wishes