Aftersales service from amazon seller Bamfive
==========
Dear customer,
So sorry to bother you,

thanks for your purchase of the from our amazon store Bamfive,

I hope that you've had a chance to try the product. 
I want to make sure that you are happy with it. 

If you are not satisfied with the product, please give us a chance to make it right! 
Respond to this email, I will do whatever it takes to make you happy.

Anything i can do for you, please feel free to let me know.
I am always here for your service.
Regards, 
