Important! Have you received your order?
==========
Dear Customer

Hope you everything goes well.
we are the seller from Ferlei shop in Amazon.

We sent you the product out very early.
May i know have you received your parcel now?

If you are satisfied with our product, 
Could you please kindly share your nice experience under the product page?
So that other customers can get a very useful information before they want to buy.
Is OK? Thanks for your kindly help in advance.

And if you have any problems about our product,
Just feel free to contact us, and then we will try our best to help you.

Please trust us, we are the honest seller,
we sincerely wish you have a good shopping experience in our shop.

Have a nice day.
Best wishes.