Imporant:May I know if you have received your parcel now?
==========
dear customer
sorry to bother you

we are the seller from richer shop.

we have sent you the item out very early.

may i know if you have received your parcel now? I am very worried about this issue

if you are satisfied with our product, we hope you can share the good experience under the product page, so that other customer can get useful information before they want to buy, this is important to us. Is it ok?

if you have any problems, you can send me the message to let us know , is it ok?
then we will offer you the professional solutions. 

we do wish our customer can have a good shopping experience here,

have a nice day.