Order information: did you received the parcel now?
==========
Dear friend,
So sorry to bother you,
we are the customer service from Senhee amazon store,

have you received the item from us?

may i know if you are satisfied with the product?

do not worry, if you have any problems, please feel free to contact us,
we are willing to give any help for you.

Have a nice day.
Best wishes.
