Important thing about your order.
==========
Dear Sir or Madam

How are you?
We are the seller from Sixrun shop in Amazon.

We have already arranged the shipment of your parcel.
May i know if you have received your package now?

If you are satisfied with our product, 
may i know if you can kindly share your good experience in the product page?
And in this way the other customers can get a great useful information from you before they want to buy, which is very important for us.
Is OK? Your kindly help would be greatly appreciate.

And if you have any problems about our product or something others,
Please kindly contact us first, then we will try our best to help you solve the matter.

Please trust us, we are the reputable businesses.
we really care about your feelings 
and sincerely wish you can have a good shopping experience here.

Have a nice day.
Best regards.