The information of your order
==========
Dear friend,
Sorry to bother you.

we are the seller from Vidoo shop.

we sent you the product out very early.
May I know if you received the item now?

If you received your product and has the problem,
Please tell us first, we will offer solution to you in time.

please trust us, we are the responsible seller,
we wish you can have a good shopping experience from our shop.

Sorry for the inconvenience.
Have a good day!
Best wishes