Aftersales service: have you received the item now?
==========
Dear friend,
Good day,
we are the seller from amazon store Xinyu.

have you received the item from us?

If you are satisfied with our product and service, we would very appreciate that you can share your good experience with others.

Or if you have any dissatisfaction, please kindly let me know, I promise I can solve it well.

Have a nice day.
Best wishes.